shopfactorydirect.com 2019-04-07

# Shop Factory Direct - Furniture, Bedroom, Living Room, Dining Room, Bathroom

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

**Shop Factory Direct Inc. - Privacy Policy**

**Our Commitment To Your Privacy:**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy the following notice explains the information we collect, how it is used, how it is safeguarded, and how to contact us if you have any concerns.

**Personal Information:**  
ShopFactoryDirect Inc. is the owner of the information collected on this site. We greatly respect the privacy of our visitors and subscribers, and are committed to protecting our customer’s privacy. We will never give, lease or sell any of your personal information, nor will we share it in any way different from what is disclosed in this statement without your written consent.

**What Information Is Collected:**  
As part of the order process, the following information is collected from shoppers:  
Name  
Shipping/Billing Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information

**Cookies and IP Addresses:**  
Like many sites, this site electronically receives and records information on our servers from your browser, including your IP address, this site's cookie information, and the pages you request. These help us identify you, monitor your shopping cart and maintain the error-free performance of our servers. Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your Internet browser to your computers’ hard drive. Your browser should already be set up to accept cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, the site will not be able to recognize your cart or your account therefore limiting functionality. We do not and cannot use cookies to gather your confidential information that may be stored on your hard drive. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

**External Links:**

This site contains links to other Web sites. ShopFactoryDirect has no control over or responsibility for the reliability, quality, privacy practices or the content of such sites.

**Address and Contact Information:**  
Our site collects information using an order form for interested parties to request information or to purchase products and services. We collect contact information, including, but not limited to, shipping address, email addresses, phone numbers, and financial information. Collected information is used to communicate with our customers with regards to their orders. This information is also used for billing and contact purposes when necessary. Customer information is considered to be an asset of ShopFactoryDirect and as such may be transferred to another company as part of an acquisition of ShopFactoryDirect Inc. This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. Any sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) relayed to us via our order form is thoroughly protected with SSL encryption, which is the current industry-standard encryption protocol.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or to comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

**Use of this site constitutes acceptance of our Terms of Use. Copyright 2007 - 2016 by ShopFactoryDirect Inc. All rights reserved.**
